[{"answer": "It resonates a great deal and in many ways, some of them complicated.", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "Is that the kind of fury that you have felt about issues over the years?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "I'm more proud to be an American than ever.", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "I mean, are you proud to be an American right now?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "I think largely people with simpler thoughts are more polite.", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "And are they?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "I don't think that that matters as much as -- in the way that it's often talked about.", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "What have been your thoughts in the last two or three years?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "We don't have to tell it to ourselves.", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "Do you think America should become -- I mean, I'll be much more selfish about his foreign policy -- be more humanitarian in areas like Haiti, but leave the bombing to other people?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "If we had waited on Iraq, what we'd be seeing is Saddam Hussein being brought down by his people right now, without hundreds of thousands of dead Iraqis, children, U.S. soldiers, all the money that's been spent that could have been spent here to better this country, to straighten this country --", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "I mean democracy and freedom, through the kind of uprising you saw in Tahrir Square, is massively more beneficial to America's interests than going into Iraq and behaving in the way that the allies did there, right?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "I think, frankly, Rupert Murdoch will be the teller of this, because I think the great despot are in the corporate world and that -- that the fact that a clown -- I mean Gadhafi, by any sober analysis, could have been three times as wealthy and a god to the world.", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "Do you think that the power of these uprisings all over the world, in all different ways, means that those guys, their days are numbered, generally?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "Well, I think I would have to begin to answer that by saying because we live in a world doing the things that -- that my organization is doing in Haiti, J/P HRO, where we have dependencies and we have great appreciation for a lot of ways in which people contribute.", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "What motivates you to go and literally get in there, live there and carry on working for this kind of thing?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "Of the Republican candidates, I would say Barack Obama.", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "Of all the Republican candidates, clearly, I suspect you're not going to vote for any of them, but if you had to, who is the one that you would prefer to see as the Republican nominee?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "That we do not necessarily be the way that I would pick it.", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "Who's the least threatening to your ideology?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "Yes, I'd like to see expectation get higher.", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "So expectation was far too high, wasn't it, given the -- the state of the economy?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "Well, I do now.", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "Did you know that?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "No problem at all.", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "Hey, bud, what's your problem?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "Have you crammed it all in?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "You know, earlier, you said something about my being a multi-millionaire.", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "Could you see yourself walking away from movies?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "Yes, exactly.", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "-- let me rephrase it, pre-divorce, right?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "Look, I -- I still have a love affair with the movies.", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "Do you need -- do you need to make movies to -- to -- to live, to earn money?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "I go to the movies.", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "Do you go to the movies?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "Not regularly enough, because I'm always traveling around and -- and --", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "Regularly?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "ENN: \"Senna\".", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "What was the -- what was the best film you've seen recently?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "Well, let's see.", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "What to you is great acting?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "Well, look, and Meryl Streep -- Meryl Streep and Meryl Streep and -- and Anna Magnani and Meryl Streep and -- no, there's -- there's several actresses that I think are wonderful and, you know --", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "Which actresses would you have?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Absolutely, Jack.", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "Would Jack Nicholson creep in?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "Well, let's see, I was -- first, I'd like to -- to erase some of my children's memories of me.", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "If you could write your own tombstone, your own epitaph, what would it say?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "Yes, aside from my kids, I don't really care if I'm even remembered, I don't think.", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "What about I'm still angry?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "Yes, we may well do that.", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "Are you going to take any action against the police?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "It was absolutely Kafkaesque.", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "Once you were both arrested, what happened then?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "Well, what happened was we were being pushed.", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "Are you completely blameless here?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "Hopefully the equivalent of the Arab Spring, I mean, in the sense that -- again, it is a way of discounting people to say they are not organized.", "docId": "111014pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "How big will it get, do you think?", "qSentId": 478}]